[Ethereal melody;
Soothing, bell-like percussion]
[Delicate violin plucking]
[Sustained, warm violin tone joins]
[Music fades]
[Wind blows, softly]
[Man] If our hair is thinning,
we shave our heads
to make the bald patch less visible?
[Man 2] Yes?
- [Man] Wrong, George.
- [George] Oh.
[Man] If our hair's thinning,
we don't shave our heads.
[George] But we don't leave
our hair long either.
- [Man] Exactly.
- [George] Okay.
[Man] Um...
Pointy sideburns.
- [George] Yeah.
- [Man giggles]
[Man] Pointy sideburns, like...
- [Man lets out funny shriek]
- [George chuckles]
- [George] Okay.
- [Funny shriek]
[George chuckles]
[Man] It's the sound they would make.
Um...
Wristwatches with large faces?
- [George] Wrong.
- [Man] Right.
[Seabirds shriek]
Goatees?
No.
[Man] Right.
The first name
of the Belgian designer Demeulemeester?
[Man narrates] My best friend's name
is George.
[No audible dialogue]
I met him ten days ago,
but we got very, very,
very, very close.
I've learned many interesting things
about Ancient Greece from George.
And he, in turn, has learned
many interesting things
about fashion from me.
- [Man] Demeulemeester.
- [George] Uh-huh.
[Man] Say it.
[George chuckles]
- Come on.
- [Chuckling continues]
Ann Demeulemeester.
[Man narrates] He is a doctor,
a brilliant one,
- attending a medical conference here.
- [Narration obscures dialogue]
We met each other by chance,
when he gave me a ride to the city.
- Say it.
- No.
Georgie, don't be naughty.
- [George chuckles]
- Um...
What about my shoes?
- Which brand are my shoes?
- [George hesitates]
- Sebago.
- [Man] Sebago? No, George.
- Don't be silly.
- [George] Hmm.
[Man] Come on, it's not even that hard.
Georgie boy, come on.
- Wow.
[George] Bottega.
[Delicate, pensive music]
[Loud, excited shout]
[Shout echoes]
[Man] Come on, your turn.
Don't be shy!
[Music continues]
George, don't be shy!
[Loud, excited shout]
Who's on that Navy ship?
Don't shoot.
[George, chuckling] Don't shoot.
[George] Thank you for everything,
these last months.
We've done so many useful things.
I don't know how to thank you.
- I must go pack my things.
- [Music continues]
[Man] Time has come to say goodbye.
[George] I'm afraid it has.
[Music concludes]
[Wind rustles]
[Man narrates] I do like George.
[Indistinct chatter]
He's the kind of man
I'd like to see naked.
I've never seen another man's dick
besides mine.
And George...
George is just--
[Loud thud, tires screech]
[He groans, tires screech]
[Agitated, indistinct chatter]
[They argue in Spanish]
- [Man 2, in Spanish] Hello, hello?
- [Woman, in Spanish] Hello. Are you OK?
[Man, in English] His blue shirt had
the smell of a fantastic, cheap cologne
- I will never forget.
- [Delicate, pensive music]
It's been six years
since our family left New York for Spain.
And all that time,
we've never quite managed to fit in.
[Music turns uneasy]
My name is Edward Taylor.
I don't write,
I don't read. I don't drive.
I hitchhike to where I want to go,
and what I really enjoy is
thinking up proverbs
and sayings that are all my own.
[Music brightens, softly]
I get a thrill from people's expressions
when they hear them,
acting like they understand when,
really, they don't understand at all.
"Banana falls down, no matter.
"Melon falls down, it's over."
I like that one.
Another one I like is:
"People are roses,
families are rosebushes.
"Rosebushes need pruning."
[Music grows, turns uneasy]
[Resonating birdsong]
- Edward Taylor.
- [Music stops]
1991...
to 2025.
[He narrates] When Mom found the house
we're living in now,
she decided to leave the cold
of the East Coast far behind
and move us all here.
The six iron deer
at the entrance of the house
- was a crucial element for her.
- [Insects chirp]
- She thought it was a sign from above.
- [Deep, metallic scrape]
Six deer,
six members of the family.
[Man walking clears his throat]
It's me, Dad.
[Man sitting] Jack.
How are you feeling, Robert?
Feeling better?
[Robert] Yeah, I'm okay, Dad.
[Jack] No, no, no, wait, wait, wait,
till your sister's
done serving this whole fish.
Okay, here we go!
[Sister] One ladle or two, Jack?
Two, please.
Thank you.
[Sister] There's no eggplant in it.
It's good.
[Robert] God, you're looking
very handsome today, Jack.
- [Jack] Really?
- [Dad] Wine, please.
Thank you, honey.
- I really mean it.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Huh.
Dad, if you could see him right now,
you would be a very, very happy father.
- Looking so fresh.
- [Dad chuckles]
Glowing.
Ed, don't you think that
Jack has been looking
really handsome lately, really sexy?
Oh, yeah. Handsome.
- Sexy, too.
- See? There you go.
I'm not crazy.
So is this new girl
prettier than our Anna?
No girl is more pretty than my 'Bananna'.
How do you like my new watch?
- Yeah, it's really very nice, Dad.
- Jack, what time is it?
[Jack, clearing his throat] It's...
- It's 10:15.
- [Dad] Oh.
Come to think of it, I don't see why
you bought yourself a new watch,
when you have so many already.
I mean really, Dad,
you can't even see the time.
[She slurps]
Says it's time for me to go to sleep.
Good night, Jack.
[Birdsong]
[Edward narrates] Moving to Spain
was a big thing for Mom,
because her favorite architect,
Antoni Gaudí was born here.
The big thing for me
and my siblings was that,
well, it's the birthplace
of Cristóbal Balenciaga.
[Uneasy, twinkling music]
[Robert chuckles]
[Chuckling blends with sniffling]
Mom's been dead almost two years now.
Her grave isn't a grave exactly,
since nothing remained of her body.
It's a statue of her naked
in the middle of our house.
Dad says she was attacked
by a pack of wolves
that tore her limb from limb.
I've often thought
what a ridiculous death that is,
to be devoured by wolves
in this day and age.
[Delicate, pensive music]
[Music continues]
[In Spanish] Good morning!
[Butcher] Good morning, Anna.
[In English] Thank you.
[Music fades]
I couldn't find anything bigger this time.
It's 13 kilos.
That's fine.
How is everyone?
Your brothers, your father?
They're good. Jack's going to come
to the shop to pay you,
if that's okay?
Give your father my regards.
Will do.
Your red shirt looks very good on you.
Thank you.
It's not a white shirt
filled with blood, right?
No. It's...
It's just a red shirt.
- Bye.
- [Jack, in Spanish] Hola, Manuel.
- Hola, Jack.
- Gracias.
[In English] The butcher
was just hitting on me.
[Truck door closes]
He wanted to fuck me,
but I wasn't into it.
But I just started my period today.
[Truck recedes]
[He chuckles]
[Birdsong]
[He grunts]
[Wet squelching]
[Shuddered breathing]
[Delicate, pensive music;
He sniffs]
[Music continues]
[Upbeat, provocative urban music]
[Excited chatter]
[Music halts;
Birdsong]
[Thunder rumbles in distance]
[Edward narrates] We placed
a makeshift cross
at the point where the attack took place,
and we leave a dead lamb
at this memorial every month
because Dad says
that if the wolves are well fed,
then they won't kill some other
poor, unsuspecting person ever again.
That way, Mom can...
rest in peace.
[Tense, uneasy music]
[Robert] Shit.
[Music halts, thunder rumbles]
[Music resumes;
Wolves pant]
[Music intensifies]
How many were there this time?
[Edward narrates] We all inherited
lots of money after Mom died.
Five.
[Edward narrates] This fact, that none
of us have to work ever in our lives
didn't affect our characters.
We always were interested
only in music and fashion.
We were all lazy,
mediocre, vapid egotists.
All of us, except for
my eldest brother, of course.
Jack.
Jack's different.
[Music continues]
[Softly] Come here.
Come here.
[Heavy breathing, soft moaning]
[Music fades;
Dog barks in distance]
[Woman, in background] Jack, it's late.
You should get up.
[Edward narrates] Jack is thoughtful
and kind-hearted,
honest and polite,
handsome and sexy, too.
I love Jack.
I'm not sexually attracted to Jack,
but I love him.
And I would do anything
to help him lead a good life.
[Jack] Where are you, my love?
- [Woman] What are you having tonight?
- [Jack] Um...
A vegetable soup.
[Woman] With butternut squash or without?
[Jack] With.
I do like a butternut squash.
It's eggplant I don't eat.
[Edward narrates] I think to myself
sometimes, you know, I think,
if there was just one person
in our family that deserves to live,
just one,
that would be Jack.
Just Jack.
[She giggles]
- Did you see that?
- [Jack, chuckling] No.
I love you.
What are you gonna do now?
My exam's so soon,
so I need to practice.
[Jack] You don't need to practice.
You're the best guitarist I know.
- I'm the only guitarist that you know.
- [Jack] Well, that's also true.
[He moans, softly]
Okay, go.
- [Jack] Love you, bye.
- [Woman] Bye.
[Gloomy electric guitar riffs]
[Door closes]
[She sighs]
[Acoustic guitar picking joins]
[Synth drums join;
Music pace quickens]
[Shaky breathing]
[Sister] Ed?
- Ed?
- [Edward, in background] Yeah?
[Music subsides]
That's it.
[Robert grunts and gags]
[Music concludes]
- Go on your side.
- No.
Hey, just let me do it.
[Robert] No.
No.
[Edward] Testing, testing,
one, two, three.
Testing, testing, one, two, three.
Edward Taylor,
1991...
to 2025.
[He changes his voice] Edward Taylor,
1991...
to 2025.
[He plays recording] Edward Taylor,
1991...
[Edward narrates] I hate the written word,
so I stopped trusting it
as a means of communication,
information and entertainment.
This wasn't some psychological
reaction to the sudden death of my mother,
- as some people have suggested,
- [Ethereal, hypnotic music]
but rather a conscious choice on my part.
[Delicate twinkling;
Music fades]
I've always considered the spoken word
to be more direct
and more human than the written.
It's what it is,
and it doesn't change.
Or if someone does decide
to change it, well, it takes work.
It takes effort.
You really have to try.
Me, for example,
I've managed to make myself
mimic the voice of Jack really well.
But it's taken many nights
of practice to be able to do it.
It's no simple matter.
[He imitates Jack] Edward Taylor,
1991...
to 2025.
[He exhales, satisfied]
[Aggressive,
electronic music plays in car]
[Music halts, engine stops]
[He groans]
[Animals call in distance]
[He sighs]
[Rocking chair creaks]
[Sister] Jack's home.
He's late.
[Sister] Because he was with that girl.
She's awful, Dad, that girl.
She's already convinced Jack
to buy her a house in the city.
Did he tell you that?
He's just gonna spend all his money
trying to make her happy.
Jack bought a house in the city?
[Sister] I don't know if they've...
closed the deal, but they will.
It's outrageous.
Him buying a house
and not asking you to go see it.
[Dad] Hmm.
I mean, they know full well you're
the greatest real estate agent ever.
I mean, it's offensive.
It's a slap in the face.
And I know it's only a matter of time
before she gets knocked up
just to tie him down.
And I just can't bear the thought of it.
And the clothes she wears are just...
awful.
I mean, you couldn't imagine
how badly she dresses, Dad.
Go fix him something to eat.
He must be hungry.
[Sister] I know she's going
to get pregnant. Just to trap him.
If she were interesting to him,
he would've introduced her to us by now.
So I'm not worried.
In fact I'm positive,
the only thing that girl has
to offer him is her cunt.
Nothing more.
Put me to bed.
[He groans]
[He breathes laboriously]
Help me into bed.
[He laughs, muffled]
You bitch.
Anna,
I never know if you're still here.
[Labored breathing continues]
[Anna hums]
I've never seen you with such an appetite.
I'm starving.
[Edward chuckles]
[Soft squelching]
You like my socks, Jack?
They're new.
Very nice.
Thank you.
[Jack] You're welcome.
Anna.
Tomorrow, make roast pork with asparagus.
- Sure.
- Or beef bourguignon.
Whatever you like.
Martha's coming for lunch.
To meet you all and for you to meet her.
[Anna] Does Dad know she's coming?
No.
[Fire crackles]
Do you want me to come to your room?
Play a little guitar
before you go to bed?
Help you fall asleep?
No. Thank you.
Are you gonna live with her?
I don't know.
[She breathes heavily]
- [She whines] What about Dad?
- [Jack] Anna.
[Anna] I mean, he just lost his wife,
- and now he's gonna lose his eldest son.
- Oh, my God.
[Jack pants]
[Robert laughs]
[Liquid pours;
Elegant piano music in background]
[Glass clinks;
Liquid pours]
[Dad] So, Martha,
what is it you do exactly?
[Jack] She plays the guitar.
[Martha] I am a contemporary
classical guitarist.
I'm just an amateur right now,
but I would love to be a professional.
Both of my parents were musicians,
piano and violin,
and I started playing when I was eight.
[Dad] Any siblings?
Yes, I have one sister.
But it's just me and her now.
Both my parents died two years ago
in a mugging in Chicago.
Yeah...
And after that,
my sister moved to Shayenne...
[She stutters, chuckles]
To... Saigon.
And... yes.
- [Fly buzzes]
- [She chuckles]
[Jack] Does a bourguignon
have eggplant in it?
[She drops the cutlery]
I forgot you don't like eggplant.
The recipe doesn't even include eggplant.
Authentic French bourguignon
does include eggplant.
It's the proper recipe.
[Dad] Anna.
Could you describe our guest to me
in your dulcet tones?
I'd like to learn more about
this girl my son has fallen for.
Dad, I can do it.
Let me do it. I'll do it.
[Dad] I want Anna to do it.
You can't be objective.
You're in love.
Unless you're not in love,
in which case
I'd be happy for you to do it.
Martha is...
blonde, very white,
- [Dad] Huh.
- [Anna] medium build,
blue eyes.
[Dad] And her handbag?
What sort of handbag does she have?
[Anna] It's a Bottega, I think.
- I think it's a Bottega.
- [Dad] Anna...
is it...
or is it not Bottega?
Yes. Yes, it is Bottega.
- Jack got it for me as a gift...
- And her bosom?
because I was--
[He chuckles, awkwardly] Dad!
No, no, no...
- Her bosom.
- [Jack] Yeah.
I can't understand why it's wrong
for me to ask about her bosom.
If I could see,
I would've already looked for myself
and I'd know if it was big or small.
And apparently that's quite alright
for someone who can see.
But then it's odd for someone who
can't see to ask for a description.
Her...
Her chest is... average.
Her chest is average.
It's average size.
- [Dad] Okay.
- Going on large.
Okay. Good.
I wouldn't say large.
Her chest is not large.
- [Jack] Well, I said going on large.
- [Anna] It's not even going on large.
[Jack] It is large.
It's... average at best.
No, they're not average.
[Anna] They're not going on large.
They're going on small.
In fact, they're maybe
the same size as mine.
They're bigger than yours.
- [Dad] Handfuls.
- They're way bigger than yours.
A handful. Two handfuls.
Two scoops. Two big scoops.
- [Anna] One handful in each hand.
- [Dad] I understand.
Please, go on.
Her weight.
Her shoes.
Her clothes.
Her nails.
Her nails...
are natural.
No polish, I don't think.
She's got a black floral dress on.
Red flowers,
probably from COS or Zara.
A Swatch watch that the time has
stopped so the watch must be broken.
And she has a Cartier ring on,
which I'm assuming
is another present from Jack.
Okay, that's enough.
That's enough.
Dad, if you continue this rant of yours,
we're leaving.
Jack.
- I'll stop.
- [Jack] I'm so sorry.
Let's eat, or this food will get cold.
[Fly buzzes]
Could somebody hand me
my glass of wine, please?
Thank you, Anna.
You know, Anna is a wonderful cook.
Yes. Jack's always going on and on
about her cooking.
She also plays the guitar wonderfully.
Completely unschooled, untrained.
She's never had a lesson,
not had so much as half a lesson
at the conservatoire.
It's innate.
[She chuckles]
It's just innate.
She's gifted.
Anna, would you be so kind as to
play the guitar for us during dessert?
I'd be happy to.
You know,
Martha and I could play together
if that's something
that you wouldn't mind, Martha.
I think we should do that...
We'll do it another time.
[Robert chuckles]
- [Robert, chuckling] Another time.
- [Delicate, pensive music]
[Edward narrates] I thought Martha seemed
like a really nice person.
She appeared to enjoy Anna's food
despite all that awkwardness with Dad.
Also, the way she gazed at Jack
showed boundless love.
I liked her. I did.
[Music continues]
[Birds shriek;
Music continues]
[He grumbles;
Horse snorts nearby]
[Robert] I'll be right there, Dad.
What's up then, boy?
This way.
- Poppies are beautiful today, Dad.
- [Music concludes]
They're blooming everywhere.
[Horse approaches]
- One, two, three...
- [Horse snorts]
[He groans]
- [Dad] Thank you honey, thank you.
- Off you go.
Straight ahead.
[Horse recedes]
I'll keep an eye on you.
Just keep your ears open, and
I'll call out if you're needed, okay Dad?
Now turn left.
I mean, right.
Your other left.
- [Dad] So turn right?
- [Robert] There's a tree!
[Frantic electronic music]
[Music fades]
[Jack] Like it?
[Martha] Yeah. Don't you like it?
- [Jack, unconvinced] Yeah!
- [Martha chuckles]
[Martha] We want a big family.
[Sweet, guitar music]
[Realtor] This house is perfect
for having children,
thanks to its large garden.
- [Martha] Jack, come on.
- Yeah.
[Music continues]
[Realtor] There are three rooms
and a primary suite.
[Switch clicks, automatic blinds whirs]
- Can we continue, please?
- [Martha] Mm-hmm.
[Realtor] And there is this
fantastic swimming pool,
but unfortunately today we can't
see it because it's being cleaned.
It really is such a nice house.
Yes, it is.
Perhaps the nicest one we've seen,
don't you think, Jack?
[Jack] Mm-hmm. Yeah, of course.
[Music continues]
[Music concludes]
- What time is it?
- I don't know. My watch stopped.
I'll buy you a new one.
An expensive one, that'll never stop.
[Indistinct conversation in Spanish]
Wanna go back to your place and fuck?
Ideally, I'd like us to buy this place
to fuck in.
So, is it doable?
[He scoffs]
- You really like it?
- Yes, I really like it.
You know,
I think the real problem is, is you...
still don't know
if you want us to live together.
- It's not that.
- It is that.
- [Jack] It's not that.
- [Martha] The house is amazing.
The price is reasonable.
So, no. I don't understand
what the problem is.
- What is it?
- The bedrooms are dark.
They are.
Jack, I'm gonna go.
I love you, but I, I...
I refuse to keep begging
for all the simple things.
So, you know...
Call me when you're sure
that you want us to be together.
Or else don't call at all.
And I'm gonna get a taxi,
- because it's only 20 minutes away.
- It's not.
Not far.
So, you have a nice day.
[Jack] It's 30 minutes at least!
You know, it's a shame
your watch has stopped
and you'll think it's 20
when it's actually 30.
[Fast-paced, deep electronic music]
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
- Night, guys.
- Night.
Good night.
Me too.
I have a very early start in the morning.
[Music stops]
Will you wait five minutes, Jack?
I wrote you a song,
and I'd like to sing it for you.
- Can it wait? I'm really very tired.
- [Anna] It's really very short.
I've got a guitar, I bought it online
and I've been practicing on the internet.
[Amp buzzes]
[Oh.
Okay.
[Soft strum;
Jack clears his throat]
Please.
[Strident single-note strumming]
[Strident singing] ♪ All the night
And all the day
♪ As I work and as I play
♪ As I leave and as I stay
♪ Up the mountains
Down the bay
♪ From Shanghai to LA
♪ As I sleep and as I play
♪ J-A-C-K
♪ J-A-C-K ♪
[He joins] ♪ ...A-C-K ♪
Dad wants you upstairs.
For the teeth brushing.
- [Jack] I'm sorry, Anna.
- [Music fades]
Would you mind singing
the rest of that for me another time?
- [Anna] Sure.
- [Jack] That's great.
- Really great.
- [Anna] You liked it?
[Jack] Loved it!
- [Robert] Good night, Jack.
- [Jack] Good night.
- Good night.
- Night.
So, do you think he liked it?
He really did, Ed.
[Guitar crackles]
Listen, Robert...
I'd like to help you, as best I can.
- [Robert] Okay.
- [Anna] And trust me...
Living in a house,
with so many men,
for so many years...
I know exactly what turns each of you on.
What turns you on.
What turns Ed on.
What turns Dad on.
What does turn Dad on?
[Anna] But moreover Rob,
only I know what turns Jack on.
- Anna, what turns Dad on?
- Which I can tell you, if you'd like.
Is it the teeth brushing?
You don't have a clue,
'cause you don't know Jack at all.
Sure I do.
[Inaudible whispering]
[They chuckle]
- That's a lie.
- That's not a lie.
Trust me, you can't go wrong.
What turns me on then, Anna?
- You know?
- Yes, I know Ed, nothing at all.
That's not true.
That rosebush out in the yard turns me on.
[Uneasy string music]
I was watering it yesterday,
and I came all over its leaves,
and then I hosed it down.
So no one would suspect a thing.
[Music stops]
[Edward narrates] Poor Jack.
It's not just me following you right now.
A stupid sister who wants to be fucked
by a butcher is following you.
A boring, sick,
and not well-dressed brother
who wants to be fucked by you,
is also following you.
A useless, perverted father
who will never be fucked again
is following you.
Blood is not only a thing
that can turn you on
but also something that can...
that set you free.
From us.
- [Woman] Please come in.
- [Delicate, pensive music]
[Music continues]
[Jack] Mom, mom, mom.
You are not plump.
You look amazing, you both look amazing!
[Music continues]
[Mother] We have chickens now.
[Jack] Yeah, you said last time.
Oh, before I forget.
- Your money.
- [Mother] Oh.
- Thank you so much, darling.
- Thank you.
[Woman] I'll leave you two to talk.
Thanks.
[She counts in Spanish, whispering]
- [Music fades]
- [Mother] So...
You know, I thought of him this morning,
when I was brushing my teeth.
- [Jack] You did?
- I never want to brush my teeth again,
so I never have to think of him.
[Jack chuckles;
Faint twinkling in background]
- You understand?
- Believe me. I understand, yeah.
- You have to get out of there, Jack.
- I know.
You're not like the others, my boy.
- You're good.
- Yeah.
- You're good!
[Jack] Well, I'll be getting
out of there soon.
- I will be.
- Really?
I met someone.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- A girl.
- Nice.
We're gonna live together.
Glad to hear it.
- Does Anna have a boyfriend?
- Anna? Are you kidding?
Such an ugly and difficult child.
- Really?
- [She laughs]
Ugly.
Before I forget, next time you come
can you bring me my watch?
- Your watch?
- The Rolex.
- You remember?
- Oh yes, sure. Yeah.
- I hope it's not lost.
- I don't think so.
I want Emma to have it,
it's her birthday next month.
- Hi.
- [He whispers] I'll find it.
- Get it.
- I'll find it for you.
Jack, have you ever heard
Emma singing?
No.
It relaxes me so much I just fall asleep.
[Jack] Yeah.
No more Xanax for me.
Yeah, no more joints.
Just her voice.
Please, Emma. Sing for us.
[Emma] OK.
[She sings sweetly in Spanish]
[Singing concludes, they laugh]
[Twinkling fades]
[Singing and laughter resume]
[Delicate, unsettling music]
[Music grows]
[Inaudible laughter;
Music continues]
[Music concludes;
Insects chirp]
[Robert] Hi.
- Hi.
- Do I look OK?
- Yeah, you look great.
- What about this shirt?
I love it, I love the color,
it's a good shirt.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Do you like these glasses?
They're CELINE.
- [Robert] Oh my God, I love them.
- You do?
They're bigger
than they looked in the picture.
I like them a lot.
- Here.
- Thanks.
[Anna] My hair is so flat.
Can you not brush your hair
with my toothbrush, please?
What's that smell?
- It's your cologne. It's OK?
- [Anna] That smells so good.
- It's a good choice.
- Works good on me.
[Anna sniffs, exhales]
- I'm nervous.
- You should put music on.
OK.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
- But not too loud.
OK.
- I'll tell him you're ready.
- Thanks. Love you.
[He grunts]
[He breathes heavily]
[Knocks on door]
Yeah.
That sounds great.
[Barking and howling in distance]
Hang on one moment, my love.
I'm on the phone.
[Anna] Robert wants to see you
in his room.
OK.
You still there?
- Hang on.
- [Music plays Paninaro, by Pet Shop Boys]
[Anna] I washed all of the dishes
and I ironed three of your shirts
so you can wear
whichever one you like tomorrow.
Thank you.
Goodnight.
Martha.
I love you more than anything
in the world.
[Knocks on door]
[Music continues]
I got my period, Jack,
can you believe it?
Give it to me.
[Robert] Jack!
[Jack] I told you to fucking grow up!
You're all fucking mad in this house.
[Robert] Fuck you, Jack.
Fuck you!
I told you to fucking grow up!
Goddamn!
[He pants]
[Music volume increases]
[He grunts]
[Music halts]
Jack?
[Howling in distance]
Son of a bitch.
This fucking thing.
Jack?
[Edward, as Jack] Dad, I'm here.
I'm sorry, I was...
downstairs, I couldn't hear you.
[Dad] Oh.
Are you a little hoarse?
Your voice sounds strange.
[Edward, as Jack] No.
Been smoking too much, I guess.
[Dad] Huh.
OK, well, I'm ready to brush my teeth.
[Water runs]
Toothpaste.
[Dad moans]
Come on, Jack, get to it.
[Dad breathes heavily]
[Dad moans]
[Moaning and brushing grow]
[He moans, laughs]
OK.
Use your mouth.
Use your mouth, Jack, I'm close.
[Intense, unsettling music]
[Dad groans]
[Edward spits;
Dad breathes heavily]
[Music fades]
Tonight was...
- Tonight was different.
- Yeah?
[Water runs]
Better or worse?
[Dad] Better.
Much, much better.
Jack.
You have no idea how much
good you do me, sweetie.
[Deep, unsettling music]
[Music halts]
[Edward] Why were you shouting upstairs
last night, what happened?
Nothing.
Just Robert playing music too loud.
[Edward] Jack.
Come here.
I helped Dad brush his teeth last night.
And now that you'll be gone,
I want you to know
that everything here will be fine.
I'll take care of it.
And I know that Mom's alive, Jack.
Followed you all the way to her house.
I won't say anything
about Mom to anyone. Don't worry.
[Jack scoffs]
Oh Ed...
Um...
[Intriguing, uneasy music]
[He whispers] Mom was never
truly happy with Dad.
He treated her terribly.
Never did her any good.
From the day they met,
he had a sneaking suspicion
Mom might be a lesbian.
But when he realized she'd fallen
in love with the landscaper, Emma...
He became a monster, he got real mad,
threatening Emma,
ripping out all her plants...
He even tried to bribe her once.
...in this yard in a fit of rage.
Unsuccessfully, I might add.
But one night,
she decided when Mom had been drinking
and Dad had called her
to put an end to this pretty tragic
situation and take her revenge.
She grabbed the flashlight.
And the moment she entered the
bathroom, where he was waiting for her,
she pointed the flashlight at her teeth.
You remember how brilliant white
Mom's teeth were, right?
Yeah, I remember.
I always wondered why your teeth
weren't as brilliant white.
- What?
- Well, I mean if...
if that theory about the combination of
Dad's cum and toothpaste was true, then...
- I think my teeth are brilliant white.
- Yeah, but not like Mom's.
- Wait, you didn't even look.
- I know, not like Mom's.
[Music fades]
They're not.
Well, anyway, when she turned on
the flashlight and shone it at her teeth,
the glare was so bright...
[Music resumes]
that Dad went blind.
Lost his sight forever.
[Music ends on quirky note]
Dad made up
that story about the wolves.
Now, I had no idea
that she was still alive
until the spring-summer, last year.
You know, in prison,
they have this system
where inmates communicate
using small pocket mirrors.
It's really amazing,
you should check it out.
Mom could've done that with her teeth.
[Jack] Hmm.
[Moaning and grunting]
[Jack] I'm sorry.
- I'm gonna cum.
- Yeah?
[Jack] Oh, shit.
[Jack grunts;
Martha moans, pants]
Ah, fuck.
Ah, shit.
[Jack pants]
Fuck.
Next time, why don't you just cum
on your way out the door?
It'll save you time.
A minute, at least.
Maybe longer.
[Jack] Martha.
I'm sorry I'm always
rushing out the door.
I am.
This nightmare will soon be over,
I promise you.
I promise.
- [Martha] Jack?
- Yeah.
[Martha] Before you leave.
I found something
in the kitchen, that I wanna show you.
You won't believe it.
Alright.
[He sighs]
Is there anything
you wanna tell me, Jack?
- What the fuck is this?
- I'm sorry.
I should have told you about it,
it's not mine!
Alright, it's...
it's Robert's.
I didn't want him to have it at the house,
so I fucking hid it here.
Look, I didn't,
I didn't tell you about it
because I thought you'd be against
the idea, and that was a mistake.
Alright? Now I can take it away
if you want me to get rid of it.
It's clearly upset you, I'll take it away.
I'll just take it away.
Why would your brother buy a gun?
It's a Taurus pistol.
Like the one they used to kill
Robert's favorite Italian designer ever.
You know how much he admires
him, and his sister Donatella, too.
- [Martha] What?
- He didn't buy it to fucking use it!
OK.
Here's the thing about Robert, OK.
- He's--
- [Martha] Just stop it, right now.
This isn't easy on me either.
I can't stand it in that place anymore.
Sometimes I wish something
would just happen, they'd all just...
fucking die.
Yeah...
Sometimes I think about the same thing.
I've even though about
the order I'd all like them to die in.
[She chuckles]
[Intriguing, uneasy music]
[Music concludes;
Door creaks]
[Edward] Hi.
I'm sorry. Look... Martha.
Listen, Martha, don't be sad, OK?
It's not worth it.
Feeling sad, I mean, like me,
a few months ago, I came across
this Comme des Garçons leather wrap
bag I'd had my eye on for ages.
It was sold out everywhere else I looked.
And when I was completing checkout,
my bank's website
went offline for maintenance,
and the transaction failed.
- I went on again two minutes later...
- [He snaps his fingers]
bag was gone.
I spent the entire next day crying.
Crying.
Then I thought about it and I realized,
there's no point crying
over something that can be fixed.
I found a much nicer bag.
The leather was softer,
it had more pockets and compartments.
And it had this...
this cross body strap. It was...
It was much more expensive,
but really much nicer.
[Martha] Mm-hmm.
It was Raf Simons.
Do you love him?
My brother, I mean.
[She sighs]
I do.
Very much.
Have you two had...
sexual relations?
He loves you very much too.
Like, of course he prefers
being with you than
having Dad's toothpaste covered dick
shoved in his mouth every single night.
I mean, everyone wants
brilliant white teeth,
but that's really a step too far,
don't you think?
Anyway, you'll see.
He'll fix everything.
And you know what they say:
"Seas in summer are warm,
but cold in...
"winter.
Seas in summer..."
Warm, summer, cold, winter.
[Edward chuckles]
Hey.
Don't lose heart.
In a few days,
everything's gonna be better for Jack.
Which means it'll be better for you, too.
Yeah.
[Martha] Oh, OK.
[He whispers] Welcome to the family.
[Edward narrates] Martha.
I think she is a really nice person,
and she's perfect for Jack.
I wasn't sure at first, but now I am.
[She whispers] Fuck.
[Edward narrates] Martha is
what George is for me.
That's what she is.
I'm sure that she is the one
that'll make Jack happy
once we're all dead and gone.
Oh, God.
[Edward narrates] Robert would do
anything for Jack.
Not because he wanted
his brother's happiness
but because
he wanted his brother for himself.
This is how I knew
that life as we'd known it was over.
Something big and strong
and bloody and sad and happy
was about to come.
And Robert was chosen to help.
Robert was chosen to set Jack free,
but he didn't know about it yet.
[Edward, as Jack] Can you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, I can hear you.
[As Jack] I wanted to say I'm sorry
for hitting you in anger the other night.
I crossed a line.
I really shouldn't have.
No.
No, no, no, no.
- Look, it was my fault, OK?
- [As Jack] No, it wasn't.
It was.
It was. I'm the one to blame, but...
thank you for the flowers
and my lovely card you got me.
[Edward, as Jack] No, Rob, I love you.
People shouldn't hit the ones they love.
That bouquet was the least I could do
to express my love for you.
So, my darling Rob,
can you forgive me?
Of course.
- Of course I can.
- [As Jack] That's really good of you.
You can't imagine
how happy you've made me.
- Rob?
- Yeah.
[As Jack] You still there?
I'm not hearing you
But Jack...
Jack, I can't hear you, either.
[Edward, as Jack] Can you hear me?
- How about now?
- I can hear you now. I can hear you.
[Edward, as Jack] I'd like to ask you
a favor, Rob.
Anything.
You could ask me for anything.
[Edward, as Jack] I'm going to tell you
what it is I want,
but I don't want us
talking about it at the house,
about this thing I'm going to tell you
because...
I don't want the others to know.
OK.
[As Jack] Is that okay?
Are you still there?
- Yeah, no, I'm here. I'm here.
- [Edward, as Jack] Great.
- I want you to go up to my bedroom.
- Right now?
[Edward, as Jack] Yeah, now.
OK, I'm on my way.
[Edward, as Jack] That's great.
Were you out dancing last night, Jack?
You're voice sounds so hoarse,
but still so sexy.
- [Edward, as Jack] Are you there yet?
- [Rob] Almost there.
Closer.
- OK, I am here.
- [Edward, as Jack] Great.
Go to my bathroom
and look in my bottom shelf.
There's a gift in there
for you from me.
Last night, I came into this sock
while fantasizing
about your bloody cunt, Rob.
The sock must still moist from my cum.
Why don't you smell it?
Do I have your attention?
[Robert] Yeah.
- I'm still here.
- [Edward, as Jack] Did you smell it?
[Robert] Yeah.
[Edward, as Jack, chuckling] Little
embarrassed to be telling you all this.
No, don't be embarrassed. There's
nothing to be embarrassed about, it's me.
[Edward, as Jack] Did you like it?
- Yes.
- [Edward, as Jack] Oh, good, I'm glad.
- [Robert sniffs]
- OK, listen to me, Rob.
There's only one way
that we can truly be together.
Do you know what that is?
No.
[Edward, as Jack] We have to get
all the others out of the way.
Do you really wanna make me happy?
You have to clear this dead wood
that's all around us.
- Do you understand?
- [Robert] I understand.
[Delicate, pensive music;
Wind blows]
[Edward narrates as himself] That night,
Robert had a strange dream
where a limousine
picked him up from the house
and took him to a beach
where a woman was lying on a lounger.
That woman was Donatella.
- Off you go.
- Alright.
[Edward narrates] He walked over to her,
stepping lightly,
'cause Donatella hates it
when people leave
careless footprints in the sand.
She said,
[Donatella] Robert,
my beautiful and stylish boy,
I know how much you admire me
and my dead brother,
both as designers and humans.
- [Dad] I'm exhausted from the walk.
- [Donatella] Robert, now that I'm not
the creative director of Versace anymore,
I must confess
how proud of you I am.
Do what you have to do
without guilt and without remorse.
Keep going.
You're doing great.
[Music plays - Paninaro,
by Pet Shop Boys]
That's it.
Perfect.
To the left.
[Horse snorts, muffled]
[Resonating exhalation]
[Hoof beats resonate]
Keep going. Come on, Dad.
Now straight.
Go straight.
Keep going. Come on, Dad!
Go, go, go.
Farther, farther.
[Horse neighs, muffled]
[Music distorts]
[Muffled, thick thud;
Music stops]
[Resonating exhalation]
[Birds chirp]
[He breathes heavily]
[Horse snorts, neighs faintly]
[Cellphone camera clicks]
Mom.
- [Mom] Hmm?
- Dad died.
- [She chuckles]
- Yeah.
Wait, died for real or died like I did?
[Jack] No, died for real.
I'll show you.
Let me find it, let me find it.
[Mom] What?
- Oh, oh. That's a lot of blood.
- [Jack] Yeah.
- See?
- [Mom laughs]
Sorry, Jack, sorry.
- How?
- Fell off a cliff on a horse.
[Emma, laughing] Stop. Stop it!
[In Spanish] How wonderful
to die like that!
- [In English] I'm so sorry.
- [Jack] No.
- Get some ice cream and stop.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Just think,
you won't have to put up with the stuff
he put you through ever again.
- [Jack] Yeah.
- Yeah.
The new house is nice?
- House is beautiful.
- [Mom] Nice.
Yeah, it's just...
I don't know, after what happened
with Dad and me leaving home,
Rob, Anna and Ed...
Stop putting others first.
I mean, come on, Jack.
Soon you're gonna have a family
of your own.
- They're grown up.
- You're right.
[Mom] I mean...
I mean... And you don't need
to come see me once a month.
I'm not the type that would take that
the wrong way.
Come once or twice a year
and bring me more money each time.
Less trouble for you and less likely
to raise the suspicions of...
what's her name?
- [Jack] Martha.
- Martha.
Martha.
- Let's talk about something...
- Yes, please.
- a little more pleasant.
- Can we, Jesus.
- I could make you the wedding bouquet.
- The what?
The wedding bouquet for your wedding.
[Jack] I don't know
if we're getting married.
[Emma] What's Martha's favorite flowers?
[Jack] Tulips, I think?
No, no tulips for weddings.
No, no, no.
- They say they bring bad luck.
- [Jack] Really?
A friend of mine asked me
to decorate with tulips and he died.
[Jack] Wow.
- Oh good, you found it.
- I did. Thank you.
- Good to see you.
Look, I want lots of photos
of the wedding.
- Oh, my God.
- And lots of video, too.
And I want a granddaughter, and soon,
a little pink cunt
created by my favorite son
would make me
the happiest woman in the world.
- Shall we?
- Yes, let's go.
- I'll see you.
- See you.
[Delicate, pensive music]
[Music concludes]
[Martha] When I was a kid,
I had this dog
I was responsible for his walks,
for his food, for everything.
Rex loved me more than anything
on this whole planet.
And I loved him back.
And at some point,
Rex got really sick.
And a month later, he died.
- [Jack] Hmm.
- [Robert chuckles]
We buried him in the backyard.
And while I was watching my Dad
digging the grave hole for the dead dog,
I could not cry.
I tried really hard.
I just could not.
And all I could think about was that
I would put those plastic bags on my hand,
and pick up his shits on the sidewalk
and throw them at the garbage.
And...
the fact that I never
had to touch his shits again
made me kind of happy
and relieved.
[Faint, uneasy music]
[He exhales]
[He sobs, strained]
[Faint, resonating humming]
[Humming continues]
[Humming stops]
[Musical doorbell]
[Ed through intercom] Yes?
[Delivery driver, in Spanish] Hi.
GSR, delivery.
[Gate whirs]
Hi, GSR.
Edward?
[He chuckles]
[Edward, in English]
Will you read this for me?
- [In Spanish] Me read?
- [Edward, in English] Yeah.
"I miss you.
"Please come see me.
"Come see my dick for real.
"I love you, George."
And then there is an address in Athens.
"Akoumantos 58, 11851,
"Athens, Greece."
[Jack] Thank you.
- [In Spanish] Bye.
- [Edward, in English] Thank you.
[Intriguing, anticipatory music]
[Edward narrates] I've only seen two dicks
in my life.
My father's, and now George's.
The size and the color of
those two dicks are quite similar, but...
George's dick looks far more well-shaped
than my dad's.
They say that all Greek men
and especially Greek doctors
have beautiful dicks.
And I guess that's true.
My sister Anna and my brother Robert,
they have never seen any dick at all.
[Music continues]
I hope they do before they die.
[Music fades]
[Mournful, intimate Greek ballad]
[Music subsides]
A long time ago,
we went on vacation to Greece.
I lied when I told George
that I'd never been.
I only said that 'cause I wanted him
to insist that I would go.
Anyway, while we were there,
Mom bought this CD with Greek songs
that we never listened to
when we got back.
The song that's playing,
it couldn't be more random,
but still, it was really sweet that
Robert chose this particular track
from that particular album
on this moment.
And it was in this moment,
sitting in that car,
looking out, listening to that Greek song,
that I realized
what he had in mind for me.
And I gotta admit, it was even better
than what he thought up for Dad.
[Music resumes]
[He whispers] I know about you and Jack.
What could you possibly know
about me and Jack?
What he's asked you to do.
What you've already started doing.
How much he loves you.
How much he wants you.
[Edward moans]
Please, just let me take you somewhere.
[Music concludes]
He visits her from time to time
to give her money.
And if he doesn't give her enough,
she gets her girlfriend to smack him.
What?
Yeah, she's a lesbian now.
I know.
Thank God you killed Dad so he doesn't
have to see what a filthy cunt she is now.
When he comes here,
she's awful to him.
She blackmails him,
she manipulates him,
she's vile, she swears at him.
No, no.
She does.
She's terrible to him, Rob.
Terrible.
If there was ever an obstacle
between you and Jack, it's her.
- It is.
- No, no, no.
This is just things
you see in your sleep, Ed.
This is like your flying shoes.
I'm telling you the truth.
The truth.
It's like they say,
"Banana falls down, no matter.
- "Melon falls down,
- [Robert breathes shakily]
"it's over."
Emma.
Do you wanna get married?
Is that a real proposal?
Yes.
I can wear my white Prada dress.
I can invite Jack.
You can cook two of our chickens.
[Muffled screaming and grunting;
Deep, unsettling music]
[Music continues]
[Howling in distance]
[Music intensifies;
Thunder rumbles]
[Music concludes;
Rain patters, softly]
[Delicate, uneasy music;
Wolves growl]
You know where you're going?
[Music concludes]
Greece.
- You have money?
- Yeah, I have money.
My passport, my pills.
I have everything.
Good.
Well, bye, then.
What about you?
You should come to Greece.
You can find me on the beach.
Oh, God, no, I hate Greece.
Probably go somewhere with Jack,
somewhere with a Dover Street Market,
so L.A., New York, London, Paris,
Singapore, Beijing or Tokyo.
Nice.
Yes.
[Delicate, melancholic music]
[Edward narrates] Did Anna ever find
that note I left her,
breaking for the first and last time,
my vow never to read
or write anything ever again?
[Music continues]
Leave the door open,
in case Ed comes home.
[Robert] Alright, I will.
Night.
[Edward narrates] See, I wrote to her
to tell her not to be sad
that the Rolex got lost.
To thank her for typing
in my credit card details
and verification codes for my many,
many online orders these past years.
I wrote to tell her that I love her...
very much.
And that she shouldn't be sad
that I'm gone.
[Music continues, faintly;
He chews loudly]
[Creak nearby]
Anna?
[She breathes heavily]
[Music concludes]
[Door slams nearby]
[He hums]
[Anticipatory, uneasy music]
Anna?
Where are you?
Anna, I don't wanna be alone.
Anna!
- [Objects clatter]
- Anna!
Anna, talk to me!
[Glass breaks]
Anna!
[Thick thuds nearby]
[Music and thuds continue]
[Her voice breaks] Martha.
Martha, can you give me Jack please?
I need you to come pick me up.
[Robert] Anna!
[Loud thud]
[Robert groans,
breathes laboriously nearby]
[He gags, breathlessly]
[Breathing and gagging stop]
[Music concludes]
[He grunts abruptly;
She gasps]
[Soft squelching;
He breathes in strained gasps]
[She weeps, shakily]
[Robert breathes in strained gasps]
[Strained gasps stop]
[Gunshot]
[Anna breathes in strained gasps]
[Gunshot;
Strained gasps stop]
[Wind whistles]
[Martha breathes shakily]
[Howling in distance]
[Delicate, uneasy guitar plucking]
[Music holds, birds sing]
[Music resumes]
[Car engine starts]
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech, car recedes]
[Edward narrates] At the end
of the letter, I wrote a postscript:
"Dear Anna, as for me I'm going
to meet my friend George in Athens.
"He's strong and gentle
and faithful and I like his body.
"We will visit Crete or some other island,
and we'll live together at his place.
"You can come whenever you like,
"and you can stay with us.
[Loud honk]
[Abrupt silence]
[Music plays - What Was Her Name?
(2025 Remaster) by David Clarke]
♪ She's in parties, what does that mean?
♪ Is she wearing the blue
The red or the green?
♪ The people she knows
♪ The things she sees
♪ She knows what's up
She's never at ease
♪ The things she sees
♪ She's never at ease
♪ Her ambitions are a well kept secret
♪ Even her friends
Don't know what she intends
♪ Out of public sight
But in the public mind
♪ What will you wear to the party tonight?
♪ Out of public sight
♪ She's in parties
♪ What was her name?
♪ Can she play the game?
♪ She's in parties
♪ Give her the floor
♪ Through the back door
♪ She walks with a limp
Tonight we fear she's lost the fight
♪ Don't pop your lipstick
Put on more lipstick
♪ Black, pink, green, red, open your mouth
♪ And they'll shoot off your head
♪ She walks with a limp
Tonight we fear she's lost the fight
♪ What will you wear to the party tonight?
♪ She's in parties
♪ What was her name?
♪ Is she into the game?
♪ She's in parties
♪ Give her the floor
♪ Through the back door
♪ She's in parties
♪ Ready to go
♪ You can't say no
♪ She's in parties
♪ She's got something to say
♪ Do you really wanna play?
♪ Give her the floor
♪ Through the back door
♪ She's in parties
♪ What will you wear tonight? ♪
[Woman recites in German;
Music continues]
[Music halts]
[Edward] 1991...
to 2025.